[

Grayjay](https://grayjay.app/index.html)

Grayjay Privacy Policy

Last updated: August 18 2023

Welcome to Grayjay. We are committed to respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets out how we collect, use, and share information when you use our Grayjay app.

1\. Scope of This Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to the Grayjay app ("we", "our", or "us") and covers our collection, use, and disclosure of your information. This Policy does not cover any third-party websites, services, or applications that can be accessed through our app, or third-party services you may access through Grayjay.

2\. Information We Collect  

**• Locally Stored Data:** Grayjay stores all your playlists, subscriptions, settings, and downloaded videos locally on your device. We do not have access to this data, nor do we transmit or store it on any of our servers.

**• Telemetry Packet:** Upon starting the app, Grayjay sends a telemetry packet which contains the following:  
  
\- Version of the app you're using and the OS SDK version  
\- A randomly generated unique identifier (this does not link back to your identity or specific device)  
\- Model and make of your phone  

**Purchase Information:** When you make a purchase within the Grayjay app, we collect the following information for tax calculation purposes:  
  
\- Country of origin  
\- Postal code (if the user is from Canada or the United States)

3\. Use of Your Information  

**• Improving Grayjay:** The telemetry packet helps us understand our user base, which devices are most commonly used, and ensures that we optimize our app for those devices. The random identifier helps us determine unique app launches without identifying individual users.  
  
• **Tax Calculation:** The country of origin and postal code (for users from Canada or the United States) are collected solely for determining the applicable tax rates on your purchase.

4\. Sharing of Your Information  

**• Limited Sharing:** We don't share the data we collect from the telemetry packet with third parties. The sole exception would be if we're legally required to hand over the data, such as in the case of a lawful request by public authorities.  
**‍**  
**• Tax Authorities:** The purchase information may be shared with tax authorities as required by law.  
**• Payment Providers:** The purchase information may be shared with payment providers where required.

5\. Security  

**• Data Security:** We're committed to safeguarding your information. While no system is 100% secure, we take various measures to protect information about you from unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction.

6\. Changes to This Policy  

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any changes, we will notify you by revising the "Last updated" date at the top of this policy. It's encouraged that users frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.

7\. Contact Us  

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our practices, please contact us at grayjay@futo.org.Thank you for trusting Grayjay with your digital content experience. We are committed to ensuring your right to privacy as you enjoy content from your favorite creators.
